reddotpayment.com 2016-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Red Dot Payment

## Privacy Policy

We appreciate your patronage of our website and we respect your personal information.  
As such, we have implemented the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) which describes how we handle your personal information whenever you visit a Red Dot Payment Pte. Ltd. (“RDP”, “we”, “us” or “our”) website, which includes the Kaleido Market website, www.reddotpayment.com, and other related sites operated by RDP (our “Website”).

By accessing our Website, you are agreeing to our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, and therefore our collection of your information pursuant to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any provision in our Terms of Use and/or this Privacy Policy, please immediately cease accessing our Website.

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without your prior notice, and your continued access of our Website signifies your acceptance of our modified or amended Privacy Policy. You understand and agree that it is your sole responsibility to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes.

**Collection of Information**

We collect information about you when (i) you access or use our Website; and (ii) you complete any registration forms on our Website.

(i) Browsing our Website

We automatically collect some non-personal information when you browse our Website. For example, we may collect your IP address, the type of web browser software used, content viewed and pages visited prior to our Website. This automatic collection is done so that we can tailor our Website to be more user-friendly and suit the needs of visitors. In order to facilitate such automatic collection, we may employ “cookies” and “web beacons”, amongst other generally acceptable web technologies.

**Accessing and amending Personal Information**

If you make a posting available for the public to view, you may not be able to alter or remove such posting. If necessary, you can email us with your request to close your account at [account@reddotpayment.com](mailto:account@reddotpayment.com), and we will terminate your account with us as well as all public postings that you have made as soon as reasonably and practicably possible. Please note that we do retain Personal Information from terminated accounts in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations, assist in any legal investigations, minimize fraud, collect debts, resolve disputes, identify issues, enforce breaches of our Terms of Use, or for any other purpose or actions as may be permitted by the law.

**Use of your information**

We use your non-personal and Personal Information generally for providing our services to you, allowing you to transact for purchases online via our Website, improving the efficiency, attractiveness and user-friendliness of our Website to you. As such, we do need to disclose your Personal Information to:-

  1. third party service providers who have a contract with us to perform the services necessary for you to use our Website, including but not limited to payment service providers who transact your credit card transactions when you make a purchase, third party sellers who will be supplying the product that you purchase, and delivery companies who will deliver your purchased product to you;
  2. third party sellers on our Website who are offering promotions or third party service providers assisting us to send newsletters and other updates about our Website and services, in which case we will only provide such third party sellers and third party service providers with your email address, but not your name or other contact details. You may also opt out of such notifications at any time by emailing us at [optout@reddotpayment.com](mailto:optout@reddotpayment.com);
  3. governmental, regulatory or law enforcement bodies who have a legal right to demand for your Personal Information; and
  4. affiliated entities and/or third parties (as well as their professional advisors) to whom RDP may sell, divest, transfer, assign, share or otherwise engage in a transaction that involves, some or all of RDP’s assets, including but not limited to your Personal Information, in the course of a corporate divestiture, corporate restructuring, merger, acquisition, joint venture, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganisation, or any other similar transaction or proceeding.

Except as provided above, we do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to third parties.

Please note however that third party sellers on our Website, and third party websites that are linked to our Website, possess their own privacy policies (of which RDP has not reviewed nor is RDP endorsing). Therefore, please do check their privacy policy before you decide to browse their websites or provide any Personal Information through their websites. You acknowledge that RDP has no control over the conduct, activities and privacy policies of such third parties, and therefore agree that RDP has no liability whatsoever in relation to the use of your Personal Information by such third parties and will release RDP from any claims that you may have arising out of your use of such third party websites or services.

**Security**

We contract only with reputable cloud computing service providers and payment gateway service providers who take all commercially reasonably measures (such as encryption, physical security, restricted access etc.) to protect your Personal Information. However, third parties or criminal organizations may unlawfully hack, intercept, or access transmissions, private communications and data storage facilities. Other visitors of our Website may also collect and misuse the Personal Information that you make publicly available (eg. via postings or reviews, etc.). We have no control whatsoever over the acts of the aforesaid third parties. Therefore, we do not guarantee or warrant that your Personal Information, transmissions and private communications will always remain private.

**Personal Information of minors**

Our Website and associated services are not directed to persons under the age of 18 or minors as may be defined by applicable law. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors, however, we are not able to ascertain on our end whether such individuals are minors. Therefore it is the responsibility of parents or guardians to ensure that their minors do not provide us with Personal Information without their consent. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her minor has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [security@reddoptpayment.com](mailto:security@reddoptpayment.com) promptly. If we become aware that a minor under 18 has provided us with Personal Information without their parent or guardian’s consent, we will delete such information from our files.

**Governing Law and Jurisdiction**

The terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy are governed by the laws of Singapore. In the event of any disputes arising from this Privacy Policy, you shall first attempt in good faith to settle the dispute amicably with us. However, if no amicable resolution is reached within 30 days, both Parties agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of Singapore.

**Our Security Manager**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, your Personal Information, or suggestions to improve the confidentiality of your Personal Information as registered with us, please contact our Security Manager at [ security@reddotpayment.com](mailto:%20security@reddotpayment.com)
